Brother, marry and remarry.
Yes, sir.
What a handsome man!
What a young man!
Why did this kind of problem start with you?
I don't know, sir.
Because I see you come from one place to another place.
Yes, sir.
Where is your wife now?
You have to pray, so that this marriage will hold. There is a man between you.
You have a spiritual husband.
Yes, it's true.
You know that.
Yes, sir.
Deliverance In Jesus' Name
This is your wife now, my brother.
This is your wife now. Before now you carried somebody's wife.
From one wife to another. But you - you only look for beautiful women.
Yes, sir, it's true.
Why are you looking for beautiful women?
I don't really know why.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Choir, please! What the Lord has joined together!
What God has joined together
Let no man put asunder
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Testimony Time
My name is Mrs. Becky Gayzee Kamibia.
I came last year because of a spiritual husband and delay in pregnancy.
Before I came here, I knew I had a spiritual husband which had been disturbing me
even before I got married.
I knew I had it because sometimes, when I was cooking in the kitchen,
I'd normally see this man in the kitchen. He would be staring at me.
So sometimes, when we were sleeping, I noticed that there was a man between me and my husband.
I'd normally get angry and at any little thing I'd flare up.
After I got married, my menstruation ceased for four years.
During the ceased menstruation I couldn't ovulate. I didn't have menstruation.
I was looking for the fruit of the womb.
We had gone to so many places but no solution.
He said we should come to The SCOAN and that I would have my deliverance.
After the deliverance, immediately as I got home, I started seeing my menstruation that month.
Shall we put our hands together beautifully for Jesus Christ!
After I saw my menstruation, we met as husband and wife and I conceived.
When I told my husband I was pregnant,
he didn't believe it. He was in the bathroom bathing.
So I just ran the tests and I told him that I was pregnant. He almost fell out of the bath.
He screamed and said he couldn't believe it.
So before I delivered this baby,
I told him where I got my deliverance and that I want that Anointing Water,
that that is my tablet and I want to take the Anointing water with me.
The day of my labour, I took the Anointing Water and I put it in my bag.
During the process of delivering, the doctor said, "The cervix is open but the baby is not coming out".
I said, "Why?"
He said the contraction was not strong enough.
So the nurses were doing something.
I said: "What is the problem?"They didn't want to tell me.
The other nurse told me that the contraction was not strong
and they didn't want to tell the doctor because they'd book me for an operation.
I said: "You should have told me, I have the medicine in my bag." She said: "What medicine?"
She said: "What medicine?" I said: "The Anointing Water".
She said: "What is Anointing Water?"
I said: "Don't you have the channel here - Emmanuel TV?"
She said: "What is Emmanuel TV?"
I said: "Don't worry. Let me deliver this baby first and I will explain it to you."
She now gave me my bag and I took the Anointing Water and I sprayed it in my mouth.
Immediately when I sprayed it in my mouth, my tummy started vibrating.
This woman said: "The contraction is coming. Madam, this Anointing Water..."
I said: "Don't worry, let me deliver this baby."
Testimony Time
The doctor now came and said: "What is the problem?"
The nurse said: "No problem."
I took some more of the Anointing Water and immediately, as I sprayed it, the baby just came out.
Testimony Time
Yes, this is the bouncing baby girl!
Hallelujah! Put your hands together for Jesus!
Testimony Time
We give glory to God Almighty, as we know that the prophet shall say
that which he shall live to see accomplished.
When the prophet prophesied into her life that she was having a spiritual husband,
that there was a man lying between her and the husband,
immediately, as we know, prophecy brings about solution.
After the prophecy, she received deliverance and we can see the result of that deliverance
to prove that God Almighty has indeed granted her that complete deliverance.
As you know, that the kingdom of our Lord and Saviour Jesus Christ, which is the Kingdom of Light,
is not something hoped for, it is a fact and when the Son of God says: "You are free!", you are free indeed.
Put your hands together once again for Jesus!
Testimony Time
And we can see you're holding a picture.
Yes.
Can you tell us what is in the picture?
This is the picture when I was pregnant.
Hallelujah! We are seeing on the screen of our television
the picture of when she was pregnant and she has really documented her testimony,
as she knew that she was still coming back to give a testimony before the children of God.
And we give glory to God that today you a living testimony of the goodness of God in your life.
And can you tell us - what is your advice to those that are listening to you right now?
My advice is for you to have faith.
When you have faith, nothing is impossible for God to do.
Yes. With faith all things are possible.
And as you know that Jesus' power to heal and deliver and set us free
depends on our faith to receive.
So let us exercise that absolute faith and confidence in God Almighty
that whatever situation you may be in, God is working out the answer.
The name of my baby is Josephine.
Hallelujah! Put your hands together for Jesus. We give glory to God Almighty.
We believe you have been inspired by the clip you have just watched.
Click here to subscribe to witness more of God's power at work in our generation today
and stay up-to-date with the latest prophecies, deliverances,
sermons and testimonies from The SCOAN.
Emmanuel TV
Changing Lives, Changing Nations, Changing the World
TT: Jacqueline Margaret
RV: Pavel Tatyana Zheleznyakov 17/11/2018 + Mel